Oh,man!
天哪
-What's that? -Treeger's snaking the shower drain.
誰啊？ 崔格在通排水管
What in the name of hell?
這是什麼東西？
Maybe he found your flip-flop.
可能是你的夾腳拖鞋
Is this porn?
這是A片嗎？
I must have hit something on the remote.
我一定是按到什麼了
Do we pay for this?
我們有付錢嗎？
We didn't even pay our cable bill.
我們連第四台都沒給錢
Maybe this is how they punish us.
也許這是處罰方式
Maybe we shouldn't pay our phone bill. Free phone sex.
也許我們應該欠電話費 免費色情電話
Maybe we shouldn't pay our gas bill.
也許我們應該欠瓦斯費
Hey,that lady's all kinds of naked.
那位小姐沒穿衣服喔
Joey pressed something on the remote and it just came on.
喬伊不知道按了什麼 它就冒出來了
It happened to me once. It was like finding money.
我有一次也按到過 跟檢到錢一樣爽
Finding money with naked people on it!
印有春宮圖的錢
But I made the mistake of turning off the TV.
但後來我把電視關掉
I never got it back again.
就再也找不到了
And I'm sad.
我好傷心
Why would he turn off the TV?
他幹嘛關電視？
The One with the Free Porn
本集播出：「為愛走天涯」
rainystar壓制iPod-Mp4
Do we really have to watch this while we eat?
吃飯一定要看這個嗎？
We don't know what could make this go away.
我們不知道它怎樣會消失
So no one touches the remote, and no one touches the TV.
所以不准碰遙控器 也不准碰電視
And no one touches the air around the TV.
連電視周圍的空氣都不能擾動
Imagine a protective porn bubble, if you will.
就像有一個A片保護罩
I'm at least going to mute it.
起碼也要靜音 不要…
We still have porn.
A片還在
What are you doing? That's too heavy. Give it here.
你幹什麼？那個很重耶，給我
Oh,God.
天哪
好了
I'm too pregnant for lugging around a stupid massage table.
我實在不能再扛著按摩桌跑了
I need a job with a smaller table.
我得找個桌子小一點的工作
Or a job without a table.
或是不需要桌子的工作
You mean,like a doctor?
像醫生嗎？
You're blocking the porn!
菲比，你擋到A片了啦
That reminds me. I have to see my ob-gyn today.
這讓我想到今天要做產檢
Emily just went to the airport.
艾蜜莉去機場了
Why didn't you take her?
你怎麼不送她去？
Her uncle had planned to do it.
她舅舅本來就打算送她
We said our goodbyes this morning.
我們今天早上道別了
You must feel horrible. Hey,the guys have free porn.
你一定很難受 隔壁有免費的A片
Hey,cheer up. You'll see her again,right?
高興一點，你們會再見面吧？
I don't know.
我就是不知道
When I brought it up,she said...
我每次提起她就說
..."This is so fantastic. Why talk about the future?
「這樣就很棒了」 「何必談到未來？」
-Let's enjoy" -Don't do the accent. It really bums me out.
「我們就…」 別學英國腔，我很受不了
Emily said I was pretty good.
艾蜜莉說我學得很好
Well,that's someone you should hang on to.
那你可得把握她
You've got to see her again.
你非再見她不可
-Why do you care? -Because!
你幹嘛在意？ 因為...
You could live out my fantasy.
你可以實現我的幻想
You had fantasies about Emily?
你對艾蜜莉有幻想？
You know,the fantasy.
不是，就是那個幻想嘛
Meet a foreigner,fall madly in love and spend your lives together.
認識異鄉人 瘋狂墜入愛河，共度一生
Is that why you hung out with that Ukrainian kid in school?
所以你國中時 老跟那個烏克蘭男生混？
Yeah,plus his mom used to put sour cream on everything.
對 另外他媽媽煮菜都會加酸奶油
Do you love her?
你愛她嗎？
We said it would only be two weeks.
我們說好只在一起2星期
You love her.
你愛她
What is love,really?
什麼是愛？
I knew you loved her!
我就知道你愛她
You go to the airport and tell her.
你得去機場告訴她
You'll probably catch her at the gate.
你應該會在登機門追上她
You'll call her name and yell "l love you!"
你會叫她的名字大喊 「我愛你」
She'll say "l love you too!"
她會說「我也愛你」
Then you will have the most amazing kiss.
然後你們會有最深情的一吻
Everyone at the gate will applaud.
登機門前掌聲如雷
I am a good kisser.
我是很會接吻
Then you two can sneak into the cockpit.
然後你們可以溜進駕駛艙
Things will start to heat up.
氣氛開始變得火熱
And then a stewardess comes in....
然後一個空姐進來…
I've been watching too much porn.
我看太多A片了
-ls that the heartbeat? -That's it.
那是心跳嗎？ 沒錯
Oh,my God!
天哪
This is so cool!
太酷了
Have we talked about multiple births?
我們談過多胞胎的可能嗎？
Let's take care of this one. If l get pregnant again,I have your card.
先搞定這一胎 要是再懷孕，我有你的名片
No,I'm getting three separate heartbeats.
不是，我聽到三個心跳音
You guys were worried I wouldn't even have one.
三個？你們還擔心我懷不成
Doctors are wrong all the time.
醫生經常犯錯
Are you sure that there are three?
你確定有三個？
-Definitely. -Oh,my God.
絕對的 天哪…天哪！
So in a few months,I'll have three babies walking around inside me?
再過幾個月 我體內會有三個寶寶逛大街？
It'll be like one of those log rides when they come shooting out.
他們出生時會跟連發炮一樣
Giving birth to three is like giving birth to one.
其實生三個跟生一個一樣
What do you know?
你懂什麼？
-Have you ever had triplets? -No. I'm sorry,I haven't.
你生過多胞胎嗎？ 抱歉，我沒有
I'm going to use this a lot.
我應該多利用這句話
菲比
How'd it go at the doctor's?
產檢結果怎樣？
You know how,when you're walking down the street...
當你走在街上
...and you see three people in a row.
看到三個人走成一列
And you say "Oh,that's nice."
你不是會說「真好」？
沒錯 好
Good news! You'll have three babies.
好消息，你們有三個寶寶
Three babies?
三個寶寶？
I've finally got my band!
我總算可以組團了
We'll have a big family! I always wanted a big family.
我們會是個大家庭 我一直想要大家庭
Oh,God,I'm so glad you're happy! I was afraid you'd be freaked.
你們高興就好 我還怕你們會捉狂
Why would we be freaked?
為什麼要捉狂？
Because it's harder to raise them and the added expense.
因為三個養起來更累也更花錢
Right.
也對
No,back to happy. Back to happy!
不，繼續高興，繼續高興
It's going to be fine...
不，沒問題的
...because I teach home ec.
因為… 我教家政
I can have 30 kids making baby clothes all year long.
我可以叫卅個學生 1整年都做嬰兒服
It'll be like my very own little sweatshop.
就像我專屬的廉價童工廠
I was thinking,ever since you said we'd have triplets.
自從你說是三胞胎，我就在想
The best thing for me to do is drop out of college and get a job.
我最好休學去找一份工作
No,you can't quit college.
不，法蘭克 你不能放棄學業
You're in college?
你在唸書？
Refrigerator college.
冷凍庫專校
When we found out we were having a baby...
當我們發現有了孩子
...I figured I should have a career,you know?
我想說我應該有份事業
And I love refrigerators.
而且我很喜歡冷凍庫
You can't give up on your dream!
你不能放棄你的夢想
No,it's okay. We're going to have three kids.
沒關係，我們將有三個孩子
And that's a different kind of dream.
那是個不一樣的夢
Three kids and no money.
三個孩子，一貧如洗
This is the boarding call for flight 009.
搭乘009班機的旅客請登機
艾蜜莉
What are you doing here?
天哪，你怎麼來了？
I had to see you before you took off.
我得在你走之前再見你一面
You are so sweet.
你真好
That's a big candy bar.
好大的三角巧克力
I had the most amazing time with you.
我跟你在一起過得好開心
Me too.
我也是
This is the final boarding call for flight 009.
009班機起飛前最後廣播
Well,that's me.
那是我的班機
Here,have this.
給你
I'm only allowed one piece of carry-on.
只能有一件登機行李
等一下
Listen,I have to tell you something.
我有事要告訴你
I've been thinking.
我一直在想…
I'm just going to say it,okay?
我就直說了
I think...
我覺得…
...I love you.
...我愛你
Thank you.
謝謝
It's no problem.
不客氣
What is that song?
這到底是什麼歌？
It's the theme from Good Will Humping.
「蜜桃捕手」的主題曲
You know who doesn't like dirty movies? My boyfriend Joshua.
你們知道有誰不喜歡A片？ 我的新男朋友約書亞
Yeah,right.
是啊
He said he prefers to leave certain things to the imagination.
他說他喜歡保留一點想像空間
Did he also say that the dialogue was corny?
他有沒有說那些對白很低俗
-And that he found it funny,not sexy? -Yes.
他覺得是可笑，不是性感？ 沒錯
Yeah,he likes porn.
他喜歡A片
Where you going?
你去哪裡？
To find out if he really thinks models are too skinny.
去看他是不是真的覺得 超級名模都太瘦
How'd it go?
他們反應如何？
Frank has to quit college...
法蘭克得休學
...because his super-fertile sister's having three babies.
因為很能生的姐姐一次懷三胎
I need to make money fast. I wanted to talk to you about an idea.
我得賺快錢 我想跟你談一個想法
You work for a big company.
因為你在大公司上班
Insider trading.
內線交易
What information can you give me?
你有什麼內幕可以給我？
They don't talk to us about that stuff.
大頭不會跟我們講這些
But I can get you free White-Out.
但我可以幫你A立可白
-Did you do what I said? -I did.
你有照我說的告訴她嗎？ 有
-What'd she say? -"Thank you."
她怎麼說？ 「謝謝」
You're totally welcome. What'd she say?
不客氣，她說什麼？
She said,"Thank you."
她說「謝謝」
I said,"l love you."
我說「我愛你」
And she said,"Thank you."
她說「謝謝」
That's not right.
不對啊
Did you say you love her?
你說你愛她？
What were you trying to get her to do?
你想騙她做什麼？
-What do I do now? -You play hard-to-get.
現在怎麼辦？ 你假裝很難釣
She already lives in London.
她已經住在倫敦了
So you go to Tokyo.
你搬去東京
Forget it.
別想了
You told her you love her. It's over.
你說你愛她，沒戲唱了
It is not over! You're over!
誰說的，你才沒戲唱
What?
什麼？
You know.
你懂我的意思
Good one.
好…說得好
It's not over. She'll call and tell you she loves you.
事情還沒完 她會打來說她愛你
Her feelings were so strong that it scared her.
她的感覺強烈到令她害怕
Go home and wait for her call. She could call from the plane.
快回去等電話 她可能會從飛機上打
But if she doesn't call, it is definitely over!
要是她沒打來， 那就是結束了
Unless,eventually,I call her to see what's going on...
除非最後我打給她探探口風
...and she says she'll call me back, but then she doesn't.
她說她會再打給我， 結果沒打
Then it's over!
那就真的結束了
Way to be strong!
真夠力
Can we watch cartoons on your TV?
我們可以在這裡看卡通嗎？
We need a porn break.
我們需要休息一下
We spent two hours watching In and Out and In Again.
我們看了2小時的 「殺進殺出又殺進」
Why don't you turn it off?
為什麼不關掉算了？
Then we'd be the guys who turned off free porn.
那我們會變成關掉A片的白癡
Yeah,but that's not what you'd go by.
別人又不會那樣叫你們
Look,I'm going to have a kid someday. Okay?
瑞秋，將來我會有小孩
And someday that kid is going to ask me if I ever turned off free porn.
他會問我有沒有關掉免費A片
I don't wanna have to tell him that I did.
我不想說我有
Did you ever asked you dad that?
你有問過你爸嗎？
I don't want to talk about it.
我拒談這件事
Good,you're here!
太好了，你們都在
What you got there?
你手上拿什麼？
This? I'm glad you asked.
這個？問得好
Don't you hate to cut a tin can with an ordinary steak knife?
用普通刀子切錫罐 不是很難切嗎？
I know what you're thinking.
我知道你們在想什麼
Pregnant woman slays four?
「孕婦發狂砍殺四人」？
-Did they make you pay for those knives? -No.
你沒買下這些刀子吧？ 沒有
-Are you sure? -No.
你確定？ 沒有
You won't make enough money by selling knives.
賣刀賺不了多少錢的
I just need enough money for the second part of my plan.
我知道 我只需要後續計劃的本錢
-What's that? -My Saturn dealership.
後續計劃是什麼？ 經銷廢棄物處理設備
Hello.
-Ross. -Emily. Hi.
羅斯 艾蜜莉
How was your flight?
旅途還順利嗎？
It was dreadful.
很慘
It was terrible how I acted when you said those wonderful things.
你對我告白 我的反應卻那麼差勁
No,that's all right.
沒關係
I'm just glad you called.
我很高興你打來
Ross,there's something that I've got to tell you.
羅斯，我有事要告訴你
There's someone else.
我有男朋友了
Does that mean the same thing in England as it does in America?
這句話在英國的意思 跟在美國一樣嗎？
She doesn't know who she wants. Me or this "Colin" guy.
她不知道她想要誰 我還是那個柯林
So I told her when she figures it out, give me a call. Maybe I'll still be around.
我叫她想清楚再打給我 也許我還在
When you say "still around," you mean still around like you might be in a relationship...
我問一下，你說也許還在 是你會等她選擇你
...or still around like you might have died waiting for the phone to ring?
還是你會等電話等到死？
But it was so right.
原本明明很完美
This isn't how it's supposed to go. There can't be another guy.
現在都亂了， 怎麼會有第三者
Of course,there's another guy!
當然有第三者
This is even more perfect.
這樣更完美
You have to prove your love!
現在你得證明你的愛
I'm not proving anything. I'm done listening to you.
我什麼也不證明 我不會再聽你的了
If I hadn't let you talk me into this...
要不是被你說服跑去機場
...I wouldn't have put my fist through the wall.
我也不會搞到去槌牆
You did that?
你槌牆？
I missed and hit the door.
結果沒打中打到門
But it opened really hard.
不過門彈得很用力
You have to go to London. You have to go fight for her.
你得去倫敦 什麼？ 你得去爭取她
That makes sense.
對，有道理
You said you loved her, and she didn't say it back.
你說你愛她，她沒有回應
Then she told you about another guy. Go to London. Scare her!
然後她打來說有男朋友 去倫敦吧，她會被嚇死
When Rachel was with Paolo, what did you do?
瑞秋跟保羅在一起時 你做了什麼？
I made fun of his accent.
我嘲笑他的口音
You sat back and let him have her. You didn't fight.
你讓他輕鬆得手 你完全沒爭取，沒錯吧？
I just told you, I made fun of him behind his back.
我說了，我私下取笑他的口音
Oh,I see.
我懂了
-You want that to happen with Emily? -No.
你想讓艾蜜莉也被搶走？ 不想
All right then,go fight for her!
好，那就去爭取她
It's like a snake pit.
好像一窩蛇喔
That could be you and Emily.
你和艾蜜莉也可以那樣
That but nicer.
比他們唯美
Go to London!
飛去倫敦
Really?
真的？
Surprise her. Don't let her go without a fight.
快點，到她家門口， 給她驚喜 別把她拱手讓人
All right. I'm going to do it.
好，就這麼決定
I'm going to London, and I'll fight for her.
我要去倫敦爭取她
Okay. Good luck!
好，加油
Can you pick me up one of those Toblerone bars at the airport?
羅斯，你到了機場 能不能幫我買特大三角巧克力
I did it! I figured out a way to make money.
我想到了！ 我想到賺錢的路子了
I'll open a massage place. Frank will help me.
我要開按摩院，找法蘭克幫忙
We'll work it around his schedule, so he doesn't have to quit school.
配合他的時間，他就不必休學
But how can you afford it?
好主意，但你哪來的錢？
We were walking down the street, and we saw your van.
我們走在路上 看見你們辦外燴的小巴
-And we realized -I'm telling it!
就想到… 我要說啦
People need transportation, and they need massages to relax.
人們需要交通工具 也需要按摩放鬆
We can combine the two. I give massages and Frank drives.
我們可以結合兩者 我按摩，法蘭克開車
I'll bolt a table in the van, and you know what I've got?
我可以在小巴裡裝個桌子 結果就是什麼？
A place that no one will get out of alive?
有進無出的死亡小巴？
Think about it. It's a taxi that people take when they need to relax.
不是，你們想嘛 就是給想放鬆的人搭的計程車
It's a Relaxi-Taxi!
叫做輕鬆任你行
The name was my favorite part!
我最想講的就是名字
-I came up with it. -You did not!
是我想出來的 你亂講
You came up with Relaxi-Cab. That's not good.
你想的是輕鬆之行 一點也不好
Oh,my god! Are you in England? Was Emily surprised?
天哪！你在英國嗎？ 艾蜜莉驚喜嗎？
No,she hasn't come home yet.
不，因為她還沒回家
She hasn't been home all night. She must be with the other guy.
她整晚都沒回家 顯然是跟另一個人在一起
I'm the stupid moron who spent the night here.
我則是在這裡守夜的白癡
-What was that? -I just put my fist through another wall.
什麼聲音？ 我又槌牆了
Tell the guys.
告訴錢德和喬伊
When is the next flight out?
下一班飛機是幾點？
About four hours.
大約4小時後
Stay there for a while. If she doesn't show up,come home.
再等一下 如果她還不出現就回來
There's a girl at the restaurant that would be perfect for you.
我剛想到 我們餐廳有個女生很適合你
Tell him about Relaxi-Taxi.
告訴他輕鬆任你行的事
Ask him if he likes it better than Relaxi-Cab.
問他是不是比輕鬆之行好
It's not Relaxi-Cab. It's Relaxi-Cab. Like Taxi-Cab.
不是輕鬆之行，是輕鬆車行 就像計程車行
That is better.
這個比較好
Do you have any 8's?
你有8嗎？
No.
沒有
Are we in London?
這裡是倫敦嗎？
Why are you here? You can't be here.
你怎麼在這裡？你不能在這裡
I've come to talk to Ross.
我有話要對羅斯說
What?
怎麼了？
Nothing.
沒事
I was going to call him
我本來想打給他…
You came to tell him you love him. I knew it!
你來說你愛他，我就知道
I was right! I'm right,right?
我是對的！我是對的吧？
I'd rather talk to him.
我只想跟他談
I've been to his apartment and he's not there.
我去過他家，他不在
I need to talk to him. Do you know where he is?
我得跟他談談 你們知道他在哪裡嗎？
Ross,are you there?
羅斯，你在嗎？
Ross,I don't know if you hear this, but I'll talk anyway.
我不曉得你聽不聽得見 不過我就說了
I'm in the States with your sister and friends.
我在美國 跟你的妹妹朋友在一起
It's all over with Colin.
我跟柯林分手了
I came here to tell you that and to tell you
我來告訴你這件事，還有…
Yes,Joey,you can have all the chocolate you want.
喬伊，你想要巧克力就拿吧
I came here to tell you that I love you.
我來告訴你…我愛你
I love you too!
我也愛你
I'll call you right now from the phone booth.
我現在就打公共電話給你
You can't hear me.
你聽不見
I wish I knew if you'd heard me.
真想知道你聽不聽得見
I suppose I've given my neighbors a good laugh.
我不是剛告白完 就是給了鄰居笑柄
Mrs. Newman,if you're listening, bugger off. None of your business.
紐曼太太，如果你在聽 滾開，不關你的事
There's not much chance you did hear that.
你八成聽不見
There's the call waiting...
而且有電話進來了
...so I should go.
我得掛了…
Oh,well.
就這樣
Ross,I love you.
羅斯，我愛你
Thank you.
謝謝
I was just at the bank. There was this really hot teller...
我剛才去銀行 有個很辣的行員
...and she didn't ask me to do it with her in the vault.
她沒有找我去金庫嘿咻
Same thing happened to me.
我也是
Pizza delivery girl comes over, gives me the pizza and leaves!
披薩外送小妹來 放下披薩收了錢就走了
No "Nice apartment, bet the bedrooms are huge"?
沒說「你家好漂亮」 「臥房一定很大吧？」
Nothing!
完全沒有
You know what? We have to turn off the porn.
你知道嗎？ 我們得把A片關掉
I think you're right.
你說得對
Ready?
準備好了嗎？
One,two,three.
一，二，三
That's kind of nice.
蠻好的
That's kind of a relief.
有種解脫感 對
You want to see if we still have it?
想不想看它還在不在？ 想
-Free porn! -We have free porn!
免費A片！ 我們有免費A片！
There's one,two and three.
總共一，二，三
-Oh,my God. -That's so beautiful.
天哪 太美了
-Oh,man. -I can't believe it.
我真不敢相信
I know.
是啊
I like the middle one the best.
我最喜歡中間那個
Don't worry, I won't let the other two know.
放心，我不會告訴另外兩個